redsheriff.com 2004-06-15

# RedSheriff Privacy Guidelines

RedSheriff’s Commitment to Privacy  
Method of Collecting Information  
Type of Information Collected  
Personally Identifiable Information  
Access to Information  
Security and Storage of Information Collected  
Changing and De-activating Your information  
Changes to the Privacy Policy  
No Contract or Liability  
Visitor Opt-Out  
RedSheriff Client Web site Privacy Policies  
Contact RedSheriff about this policy

RedSheriff is fully committed to upholding its Privacy Policy. Providing the company with your personal information is an act of trust; an act that is taken very seriously in the way that RedSheriff operates. The RedSheriff Privacy Policy will outline details on how information is collected and used. Information is also provided on how to change or de-activate your data. 

The term "RedSheriff Client Web sites" is used throughout this Privacy Policy and refers to Web sites of clients in addition to the RedSheriff Corporate Web site. This Privacy Policy may have even been accessed through a link from a RedSheriff Client Web site. 

"Cookies" may be used to gather statistical information that will assist in understanding what users find interesting and useful on client Web sites. These cookies are known as your "Unique Visitor Cookie", a small piece of data, identifying you only by random number (e.g. #12489). No personal information can be identified about the user through cookies. This numerical data is sent to your browser from a Web server and then stored onto your computer's hard drive. Through modification of browser preferences, a user can elect to accept all cookies, receive notification when a cookie is set or decline all cookies. Alterations to these settings may, however, affect the functionality of RedSheriff Client Web sites. 

A piece of code may also be embedded into pages of certain client Web sites. This provides statistical site usage information relating solely to Internet usage behavior. RedSheriff does not and will not use this code to collect any personally identifiable information. 

When visiting a RedSheriff Client Web site, general information that will not personally identify you may be collected. Types of information include data about pages visited, duration of page view, location previous to accessing the RedSheriff Client Web site, navigational habits of users along with details on browser (including Internet Protocol 'IP' addresses or browser configurations) and operating systems. This information alone does not identify an individual and will not be combined with information that can trace back to a specific individual. Instead, it provides statistics that are used to analyze and improve RedSheriff Client Web sites. Through this "Aggregate Statistical Data," insight and a greater understanding of how people respond to RedSheriff Client Web sites can be gained while concealing all personally identifiable or sensitive data. 

Personally identifiable information is defined as any personal information that could identify you such as your name, address, telephone number, billing and shipping information, credit card information or e-mail address. 

Generally, when you visit a RedSheriff Client Web site, you are not required to disclose who you are or reveal any personally identifiable information. Since RedSheriff takes your privacy seriously, no personally identifiable information will be collected unless it is voluntarily provided. At no time during your visit to a RedSheriff Client Web site should you feel obligated to reveal any personal information to RedSheriff. 

At some RedSheriff Client Web sites, a pop-up window may invite you to answer survey questions and provide certain demographic information such as your age, sex, income bracket, country of access and location of connection (e.g. home or work). Response to these windows is voluntary. If you choose to provide your demographic information, another cookie will be set which will link to your Unique Visitor Cookie. The result of these two sources of information is your "Site Usage Information". (Refer to "Method of Collecting Information" for more information). 

In some circumstances, RedSheriff may request that demographic information be provided in order to participate in certain promotions, receive product information or buy products offered through RedSheriff Client Web sites. RedSheriff may also seek personal information in order to verify whether you have already completed a survey or questionnaire. The primary goal in collecting personally identifiable information is to provide a better understanding of your needs to clients. 

Personally identifiable information is forwarded to clients only if your consent is received. This information allows clients to perform various functions including-but not limited to-analysis of site usage (who has visited the site and what they are interested in), customizing the advertising or content seen by users in addition to improving marketing and promotional efforts. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by RedSheriff; no representation whatsoever is made concerning the policies of clients. Users are encouraged to read the privacy statements of any Web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

RedSheriff will not sell or provide any personal details in its possession to a mailing list. Personal information may be shared with third party suppliers and service providers including independent contractors providing services for or with RedSheriff. In all cases, these third parties are contractually required to keep that information confidential. They are not authorized by RedSheriff to use that information for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for or with RedSheriff. Information may be disclosed to third parties if consent is received, if we are compelled or authorized to do so by Law, or if there is a reasonable belief that there is a threat to someone's life or health. 

The RedSheriff Web site contains an opt-in mailing list which requests receipt of a monthly Newsletter. You may voluntarily choose to receive this correspondence. To remove your name from the mailing list, simply unsubscribe by sending an email to [newsletter@redsheriff.com](mailto:newsletter@redsheriff.com). 

Personally identifiable information submitted for employment purposes will only be used in connection with the application process. It will not be used or disclosed for any other purposes unless required or authorized by Law. In this case, the disclosure of information may be required if RedSheriff is compelled or authorized to do so by Legal Authorities or if there is a reasonable belief that there is a threat to an individual's life or health. 

RedSheriff is committed to maintaining the security of data collected and protecting it from loss, misuse or alteration. This applies to demographic information, client site usage information and personally identifiable information. Data collected is stored on secure RedSheriff servers that can be accessed by authorized RedSheriff personnel only. To safeguard all information collected, RedSheriff and its employees follow the practices in this Policy. Access or use of information for any purpose other than those explained in this Policy will not be authorized. 

If you would like to change or de-activate any personally identifiable information you have submitted to RedSheriff, please send a request to [privacy@redsheriff.com](mailto:privacy@redsheriff.com) As soon as your request is received, RedSheriff will change or de-activate any information that could be used to identify you unless disclosure is required or authorized by Law. Once de-activated, your data will no longer be accessible. However, due to limitations imposed by system backups to magnetic media including the off-site secure storage of data from our data warehouse, data can (in some circumstances) remain on these tapes. In the unlikely event that one of these tapes is accessed as part of a larger recovery of RedSheriff data, your data would continue to be flagged and remain de-activated and inaccessible for use by RedSheriff staff. 

To fully protect your privacy, RedSheriff reserves the right to amend this Policy at any time and for any reason. Amended terms will be posted via the RedSheriff Web site as they occur and you are encouraged to check back frequently for updates. This Privacy and Cookie Policy was last amended on December 22nd, 2003. 

Nothing contained in this Policy is intended to create a contract or agreement between RedSheriff and any user providing identifiable information in any form, whether visiting this site or any RedSheriff Client site. All necessary steps will be taken to comply with this Privacy Policy, but to the extent permitted by Law, nothing in this policy is intended to hold RedSheriff liable for any failure to comply with this policy. Given that RedSheriff does not control the Privacy practices of clients, it is advised that you read and fully understand their Privacy Policies. 

At RedSheriff, we believe in giving you the freedom to choose. In line with this belief, we offer you the following options:

**Anonymous User**

RedSheriff will continue to collect and use certain information about your behaviour on a RedSheriff Client Web site. However, the data collected will only ever be presented as part of a pool of general, ‘Anonymous Users’ and information such as the path you took within the site will not be collected and processed.

[Click here](http://server-us.imrworldwide.com/cgi-bin/o?oo=anon&tu=http://www.redsheriff.com/us/content/privacy_1_1.html) if you wish to be an Anonymous User.

**Total Opt-Out**

RedSheriff will not collect any data at all regarding your behaviour on a RedSheriff Client Web site. RedSheriff will however record the fact that a ‘Total Opt-Out’ selection has been made, so that aggregated totals of ‘Total Opt-Out’ figures can be calculated and recorded.

[Click here](http://server-us.imrworldwide.com/cgi-bin/o?oo=total&tu=http://www.redsheriff.com/us/content/privacy_1_2.html) if you wish to be a Total Opt-Out User.

Please note: If you regularly delete all your Cookies, you will need to opt-out each time your Cookie are deleted.

**Cancel Opt-Out**

[Click here](http://server-us.imrworldwide.com/cgi-bin/o?oo=cancel&tu=http://www.redsheriff.com/us/content/privacy_1_3.html) if you wish to be issued with a new RedSheriff cookie to enable data collection.

Given that RedSheriff does not control the Privacy practices of clients, it is advised that you read and fully understand their Privacy Policies. 

If you have any questions or comments regarding this policy, please contact RedSheriff at [privacy@redsheriff.com](mailto:privacy@redsheriff.com) or +1 212 905 6115\.
